<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Personal Cookbook App</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="re_password">Retype Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="log_in">Already have an account? Log In</string>
    <string name="log_in_now">Log In</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_account">AccountActivity</string>
    <string name="open_nav">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_nav">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="pasta_carbonara_ingredients">• 1 pound spaghetti\n• ½ pound pancetta, diced\n• 4 large egg yolks\n• 1 cup freshly grated Pecorino Romano cheese\n• ½ cup freshly grated Parmesan cheese\n• 4 cloves garlic, minced\n• Salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste\n• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• (optional) Chopped parsley, for garnish</string>
    <string name="pasta_carbonara_instructions">1. Bring a large pot of salted water to a boil. Add spaghetti and cook until al dente, about 8–10 minutes.\n\n2. Meanwhile, heat olive oil in a large skillet over medium heat. Add pancetta and cook, stirring occasionally, until crispy, about 8–10 minutes. Add garlic and cook for another minute.\n\n3. In a medium bowl, whisk together egg yolks, Pecorino Romano cheese, and Parmesan cheese until well combined.\n\n4. Drain spaghetti and reserve 1 cup of pasta water.\n\n5. Return the skillet with pancetta to low heat. Add the spaghetti and toss with the pancetta and garlic until well combined.\n\n6. Remove the skillet from heat and add the egg yolk mixture. Use tongs to toss the pasta quickly to prevent the eggs from scrambling. Add pasta water as needed to create a smooth and creamy sauce.\n\n7. Season with salt and pepper to taste.\n\n8. Serve immediately with chopped parsley as garnish, if desired.</string>

    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="discover_restaurants">Discover Restaurants</string>
    <string name="menu">MENU</string>
    <string name="pasta_carbonara_recipe_intro">Pasta Carbonara is a classic Italian dish that\'s both hearty and delicious. With crispy pancetta and a creamy, cheesy sauce, this medium-difficulty recipe is sure to become a new favorite in your repertoire. With just a few simple ingredients and some basic cooking techniques, you can whip up a batch of pasta carbonara that\'s perfect for any occasion. So why not give it a try and impress your friends and family with this tasty and satisfying meal?</string>
    <string name="pasta_carbonara_image">pasta carbonara image</string>
    <string name="balsamic_caprese_recipe_intro">Looking for a quick and easy appetizer or light lunch option? Look no further than this delicious balsamic caprese salad! Featuring fresh tomatoes, creamy mozzarella, and fragrant basil, this classic Italian dish is elevated with a simple yet flavorful balsamic dressing. This easy recipe comes together in just minutes, making it perfect for busy weeknights or last-minute entertaining. So grab your ingredients and get ready to enjoy a taste of Italy right in your own home!</string>
    <string name="balsamic_caprese_image">balsamic caprese image</string>
    <string name="balsamic_caprese_ingredients">• 2 large ripe tomatoes, sliced\n• 8 oz fresh mozzarella cheese, sliced\n• ¼ cup fresh basil leaves\n• 2 tbsp balsamic vinegar\n• 2 tbsp olive oil\n• Salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste</string>
    <string name="balsamic_caprese_instructions">1. Arrange the tomato slices and mozzarella slices on a serving platter, alternating between them.\n\n2. Top the slices with fresh basil leaves.\n\n3. In a small bowl, whisk together the balsamic vinegar and olive oil until well combined.\n\n4. Drizzle the dressing over the tomato and mozzarella slices.\n\n5. Season with salt and freshly ground black pepper to taste.\n\n6. Serve immediately and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli_recipe_intro">Looking for a delicious and satisfying dinner idea? Look no further than this easy beef broccoli stir-fry recipe! Tender strips of beef are combined with crisp broccoli florets in a flavorful sauce that\'s both sweet and savory. With just a few simple ingredients and basic cooking techniques, you can whip up a restaurant-quality meal in the comfort of your own home. This recipe is perfect for busy weeknights when you want something tasty and filling without spending hours in the kitchen. So why not give it a try and impress your family and friends with your culinary skills?</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli_image">beef broccoli image</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli_ingredients">• 1 lb flank steak, sliced thinly\n• 4 cups broccoli florets\n• 2 tbsp vegetable oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• ½ tsp ginger, grated\n• ¼ cup soy sauce\n• ¼ cup oyster sauce\n• ¼ cup brown sugar\n• ½ cup water\n• 1 tbsp cornstarch\n• Salt and pepper, to taste</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli_instructions">1. Heat the vegetable oil in a large skillet or wok over high heat. Add the sliced flank steak and stir–fry for 3–4 minutes, or until browned.\n\n2. Remove the steak from the skillet and set aside.\n\n3. Add the broccoli florets to the skillet and stir–fry for 3–4 minutes, or until they are bright green and slightly tender.\n\n4. Add the minced garlic and grated ginger to the skillet and stir–fry for 30 seconds, or until fragrant.\n\n5. In a small bowl, whisk together the soy sauce, oyster sauce, brown sugar, water, and cornstarch until smooth.\n\n6. Add the steak back to the skillet and pour the sauce over the top.\n\n7. Stir everything together and cook for an additional 2–3 minutes, or until the sauce has thickened and the steak is fully cooked.\n\n8. Season with salt and pepper to taste.\n\n9. Serve the beef broccoli stir-fry over rice or noodles and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="blueberry_scones_recipe_intro">Start your morning off right with these delicious and easy-to-make blueberry scones! Perfectly tender and flaky, these scones are packed with juicy blueberries and just the right amount of sweetness. Whether you enjoy them with your morning coffee or as an afternoon snack, these scones are sure to become a new favorite in your household.</string>
    <string name="blueberry_scones_image">blueberry scones image</string>
    <string name="blueberry_scones_ingredients">• 2 cups all-purpose flour\n• ⅓ cup granulated sugar\n• 2 tsp baking powder\n• ½ tsp salt\n• ½ cup unsalted butter, cold and cubed\n• ½ cup milk\n• 1 egg\n• 1 tsp vanilla extract\n• 1 cup fresh blueberries</string>
    <string name="blueberry_scones_instructions">1. Preheat your oven to 400°F (200°C) and line a baking sheet with parchment paper.\n\n2. In a large mixing bowl, whisk together the flour, sugar, baking powder, and salt.\n\n3. Add the cold butter to the bowl and use a pastry cutter or your fingers to work the butter into the flour mixture until it resembles coarse crumbs.\n\n4. In a separate bowl, whisk together the milk, egg, and vanilla extract.\n\n5. Add the wet ingredients to the dry ingredients and stir until just combined.\n\n6. Gently fold in the fresh blueberries.\n\n7. Turn the dough out onto a floured surface and pat it into a circle about 1 inch thick.\n\n8. Cut the circle into 8 equal wedges and transfer them to the prepared baking sheet.\n\n9. Bake the scones for 15–18 minutes, or until they are golden brown and a toothpick inserted into the center comes out clean.\n\n10. Allow the scones to cool on the baking sheet for a few minutes before transferring them to a wire rack to cool completely.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_recipe_intro">Indulge in a slice of heaven with this creamy and delicious cheesecake recipe. Made with a buttery graham cracker crust and a velvety smooth cream cheese filling, this cheesecake is the perfect dessert for any occasion. Topped with your favorite fruit or chocolate sauce, this cheesecake is sure to impress.</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_image">cheesecake image</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_ingredients">For the crust:\n• 1 ½ cups graham cracker crumbs\n• ¼ cup granulated sugar\n• ⅓ cup unsalted butter, melted\nFor the filling:\n• 4 (8 oz.) packages cream cheese, softened\n• 1 ¼ cups granulated sugar\n• 2 tsp vanilla extract\n• 4 large eggs\n• ⅓ cup heavy cream</string>
    <string name="cheesecake_instructions">1. Preheat your oven to 350°F (175°C) and grease a 9–inch springform pan.\n\n2. In a mixing bowl, combine the graham cracker crumbs, sugar, and melted butter until well combined.\n\n3. Press the mixture into the bottom of the prepared pan and bake for 10 minutes.\n\n4. In a separate mixing bowl, beat the cream cheese until smooth.\n\n5. Gradually add in the sugar and vanilla extract, and beat until well combined.\n\n6. Add the eggs, one at a time, beating well after each addition.\n\n7. Stir in the heavy cream until just combined.\n\n8. Pour the mixture into the prepared crust and bake for 45–50 minutes, or until the center is almost set.\n\n9. Remove the cheesecake from the oven and allow it to cool to room temperature.\n\n10. Refrigerate the cheesecake for at least 4 hours or overnight before serving.</string>
    <string name="chocolate_smoothie_recipe_intro">Start your day off right with this rich and creamy Chocolate Peanut Butter Banana Smoothie. Made with wholesome ingredients like bananas, peanut butter, and cocoa powder, this smoothie is the perfect breakfast or snack. It\'s a great way to satisfy your sweet tooth while getting a boost of protein and fiber.</string>
    <string name="chocolate_smoothie_ingredients">• 2 ripe bananas\n• 1 cup unsweetened almond milk\n• ¼ cup creamy peanut butter\n• 2 tbsp cocoa powder\n• 1 tbsp honey\n• ½ tsp vanilla extract\n• 1 cup ice cubes</string>
    <string name="chocolate_smoothie_image">chocolate smoothie image</string>
    <string name="chocolate_smoothie_instructions">1. Peel the bananas and cut them into chunks.\n\n2. Place the banana chunks, almond milk, peanut butter, cocoa powder, honey, and vanilla extract in a blender.\n\n3. Add the ice cubes to the blender and blend on high speed until smooth and creamy.\n\n4. Taste the smoothie and adjust the sweetness or thickness as desired by adding more honey or ice cubes.\n\n5. Pour the smoothie into glasses and serve immediately.</string>
    <string name="grilled_octopus_recipe_intro">Grilled octopus is a popular dish in many Mediterranean countries and for good reason - it\'s delicious! Tender and packed with flavor, this grilled octopus recipe is perfect for a summer barbecue or a special dinner. Impress your guests with this unique and flavorful seafood dish.</string>
    <string name="grilled_octopus_image">grilled octopus image</string>
    <string name="grilled_octopus_ingredients">• 1 large octopus (about 2 pounds)\n• ¼ cup olive oil\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 2 tbsp lemon juice\n• 1 tsp dried oregano\n• Salt and pepper, to taste</string>
    <string name="grilled_octopus_instructions">1. Clean the octopus by removing the head, beak, and eyes, and discarding the innards. Rinse the octopus well under cold running water.\n\n2. Bring a large pot of salted water to a boil. Dip the octopus into the boiling water 3 times, holding it by the head each time, and then submerge it completely in the water. Reduce the heat to low and simmer for about 45 minutes, or until the octopus is tender.\n\n3. Preheat the grill to medium–high heat.\n\n4. In a small bowl, whisk together the olive oil, garlic, lemon juice, oregano, salt, and pepper.\n\n5. Remove the octopus from the pot and let it cool slightly. Cut the octopus into pieces and brush with the olive oil mixture.\n\n6. Place the octopus pieces on the grill and cook for 2–3 minutes per side, or until lightly charred and heated through.\n\n7. Serve the grilled octopus hot with additional lemon wedges and a drizzle of olive oil.</string>
    <string name="habanero_skewers_recipe_intro">These Habanero Skewers are perfect for those who love a little heat in their food. With a mix of vegetables and chicken marinated in a spicy habanero sauce, these skewers are sure to impress your taste buds. They\'re perfect for a summer barbecue or any time you\'re in the mood for some fiery and delicious food.</string>
    <string name="habanero_skewers_image">habanero skewers image</string>
    <string name="habanero_skewers_ingredients">• 2 habanero peppers, seeded and finely chopped\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• ¼ cup olive oil\n• 2 tbsp lime juice\n• 1 tsp honey\n• ½ tsp smoked paprika\n• ½ tsp ground cumin\n• Salt and pepper, to taste\n• 1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breast, cut into cubes\n• 1 red bell pepper, seeded and cut into chunks\n• 1 yellow bell pepper, seeded and cut into chunks\n• 1 red onion, cut into chunks\n• 8 skewers (if using wooden skewers, soak in water for 30 minutes before grilling)</string>
    <string name="habanero_skewers_instructions">1. In a small bowl, whisk together the habanero peppers, garlic, olive oil, lime juice, honey, smoked paprika, cumin, salt, and pepper.\n\n2. Place the chicken in a large resealable plastic bag and pour the marinade over the chicken. Seal the bag and marinate in the refrigerator for at least 30 minutes, or up to 4 hours.\n\n3. Preheat the grill to medium–high heat.\n\n4. Thread the chicken, bell peppers, and red onion onto the skewers.\n\n5. Grill the skewers for 10–12 minutes, turning occasionally, or until the chicken is cooked through.\n\n6. Serve the Habanero Skewers hot with additional lime wedges and a sprinkle of chopped fresh cilantro.</string>
    <string name="lemon_shrimp_recipe_intro">This Lemon Shrimp recipe is a delicious and healthy meal that\'s perfect for busy weeknights. The shrimp are cooked in a lemon and garlic sauce and served with a side of steamed vegetables or rice. The tangy and fresh flavors of lemon and garlic pair perfectly with succulent shrimp, making this dish a crowd-pleaser.</string>
    <string name="lemon_shrimp_image">lemon shrimp image</string>
    <string name="lemon_shrimp_ingredients">• 1 pound large shrimp, peeled and deveined\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 garlic cloves, minced\n• ¼ teaspoon red pepper flakes\n• ¼ teaspoon salt\n• ¼ teaspoon black pepper\n• 2 tablespoons lemon juice\n• ¼ cup chopped fresh parsley</string>
    <string name="lemon_shrimp_instructions">1. In a large bowl, combine the shrimp, olive oil, garlic, red pepper flakes, salt, and black pepper. Stir to coat the shrimp with the seasoning.\n\n2. Heat a large skillet over medium–high heat. Add the shrimp to the skillet and cook for 2–3 minutes on each side, until pink and cooked through.\n\n3. Remove the skillet from the heat and stir in the lemon juice and chopped parsley. Toss the shrimp in the sauce until they are coated evenly.\n\n4. Serve the Lemon Shrimp hot with a side of steamed vegetables or rice.</string>
    <string name="mushroom_pizza_recipe_intro">This Mushroom Pizza recipe is a vegetarian twist on the classic Italian favorite. Loaded with savory mushrooms and tangy cheese, this pizza is a crowd-pleaser that\'s easy to make and perfect for any occasion.</string>
    <string name="mushroom_pizza_image">mushroom pizza image</string>
    <string name="mushroom_pizza_ingredients">•1 pound pizza dough\n• ½ cup pizza sauce\n• ½ pound mushrooms, sliced\n• 2 cups shredded mozzarella cheese\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 1 tablespoon dried oregano\n• Salt and pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="mushroom_pizza_instructions">1. Preheat the oven to 425°F (220°C). Grease a large pizza pan or baking sheet.\n\n2. Roll out the pizza dough on a floured surface and transfer it to the prepared pan or sheet.\n\n3. Spread the pizza sauce over the dough, leaving a ½ inch border around the edges.\n\n4. Arrange the sliced mushrooms over the sauce and sprinkle the shredded mozzarella cheese on top.\n\n5. Drizzle the pizza with olive oil and sprinkle with oregano, salt, and pepper to taste.\n\n6. Bake the pizza in the preheated oven for 12–15 minutes, or until the crust is golden brown and the cheese is melted and bubbly.\n\n7. Remove the pizza from the oven and let it cool for a few minutes before slicing and serving.</string>
    <string name="peachburrata_salad_recipe_intro">This Peach &amp; Burrata Salad recipe is a delicious combination of sweet and savory flavors. The juicy peaches, creamy burrata cheese, and tangy balsamic glaze make for a perfect summer salad that\'s easy to make and always a crowd-pleaser.</string>
    <string name="peachburrata_salad_image">peach burrata salad image</string>
    <string name="peachburrata_salad_ingredients">• 4 ripe peaches, sliced\n• 8 ounces fresh burrata cheese, torn into small pieces\n• 4 cups mixed greens\n• ¼ cup chopped fresh basil\n• ¼ cup balsamic glaze\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• Salt and pepper to taste</string>
    <string name="peachburrata_salad_instructions">1. In a large bowl, toss together the sliced peaches, mixed greens, and chopped basil.\n\n2. Add the torn burrata cheese and gently mix to combine.\n\n3. In a small bowl, whisk together the balsamic glaze and olive oil. Drizzle the dressing over the salad and toss gently to coat.\n\n4. Season the salad with salt and pepper to taste.\n\n5. Serve the Peach &amp; Burrata Salad immediately, garnished with additional chopped basil if desired.</string>
    <string name="polenta_recipe_intro">Polenta is a classic Italian dish that\'s creamy, comforting, and versatile. This recipe features a simple yet delicious combination of polenta, butter, and Parmesan cheese. It\'s the perfect side dish for a variety of main courses and is sure to become a staple in your recipe repertoire.</string>
    <string name="polenta_image">polenta image</string>
    <string name="polenta_ingredients">• 1 cup yellow cornmeal\n• 4 cups water\n• 1 teaspoon salt\n• 2 tablespoons unsalted butter\n• ½ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• Freshly ground black pepper</string>
    <string name="polenta_instructions">1. In a medium saucepan, bring the water to a boil. Add the salt.\n\n2. Slowly pour in the cornmeal while whisking continuously to prevent lumps.\n\n3. Reduce the heat to low and cook the polenta for about 15–20 minutes, stirring occasionally, until it thickens and pulls away from the sides of the pan.\n\n4. Remove the polenta from the heat and stir in the butter and Parmesan cheese until melted and well combined.\n\n5. Season the polenta with freshly ground black pepper to taste.\n\n6. Serve the polenta hot, as a side dish or topped with your favorite sauce or toppings.</string>
    <string name="quinoa_chili_recipe_intro">This hearty and healthy quinoa chili is perfect for a cold evening or when you\'re craving a satisfying, plant-based meal. Packed with protein and fiber, this chili is a great way to incorporate quinoa and veggies into your diet.</string>
    <string name="quinoa_chili_image">quinoa chili image</string>
    <string name="quinoa_chili_ingredients">• 1 tablespoon olive oil\n• 1 onion, diced\n• 3 cloves garlic, minced\n• 1 red bell pepper, diced\n• 1 green bell pepper, diced\n• 1 zucchini, diced\n• 1 cup uncooked quinoa, rinsed\n• 1 can (14.5 ounces) diced tomatoes\n• 1 can (15 ounces) kidney beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 can (15 ounces) black beans, drained and rinsed\n• 1 tablespoon chili powder\n• 1 teaspoon cumin\n• ½ teaspoon smoked paprika\n• Salt and pepper to taste\n• 4 cups vegetable broth\n• Optional toppings: shredded cheese, sour cream, diced avocado, chopped cilantro, sliced jalapenos</string>
    <string name="quinoa_chili_instructions">1. In a large pot, heat the olive oil over medium heat. Add the onion and garlic and cook until the onion is translucent, about 5 minutes.\n\n2. Add the red and green bell peppers and zucchini and cook for another 5 minutes, until the vegetables are slightly softened.\n\n3. Stir in the quinoa, diced tomatoes, kidney beans, black beans, chili powder, cumin, smoked paprika, salt, and pepper. Pour in the vegetable broth and bring the mixture to a boil.\n\n4. Reduce the heat to low, cover the pot, and simmer for 25–30 minutes, or until the quinoa is cooked and the vegetables are tender.\n\n5. Taste and adjust seasonings as needed. Serve hot with desired toppings.</string>
    <string name="raspberry_cheesecake_bars_recipe_intro">These Raspberry Cheesecake Bars are a delightful treat that combine the creaminess of cheesecake with the tartness of raspberries. The buttery crust and sweet raspberry jam add an extra layer of flavor to these bars that are perfect for any occasion.</string>
    <string name="raspberry_cheesecake_bars_image">raspberry cheesecake bars image</string>
    <string name="raspberry_cheesecake_bars_ingredients">• 1 cup all-purpose flour\n• ⅓ cup granulated sugar\n• ½ cup unsalted butter, softened\n• 1 (8 oz) package cream cheese, softened\n• ¼ cup granulated sugar\n• 1 large egg\n• 1 tsp vanilla extract\n• ¼ cup seedless raspberry jam\n• ½ cup fresh raspberries</string>
    <string name="raspberry_cheesecake_bars_instructions">1. Preheat oven to 350°F (175°C). Line an 8–inch square baking pan with parchment paper, leaving an overhang on two sides.\n\n2. In a medium bowl, combine the flour, sugar, and softened butter until a crumbly dough forms. Press the dough into the bottom of the prepared baking pan.\n\n3. Bake the crust for 15–20 minutes or until lightly golden brown.\n\n4. Meanwhile, in a separate bowl, beat together the cream cheese, sugar, egg, and vanilla extract until smooth and creamy.\n\n5. Pour the cheesecake mixture over the baked crust and spread evenly.\n\n6. Dollop spoonfuls of raspberry jam onto the cheesecake mixture and swirl with a knife or toothpick.\n\n7. Sprinkle fresh raspberries on top.\n\n8. Bake for 25–30 minutes or until set.\n\n9. Allow the bars to cool completely in the pan.\n\n10. Use the parchment paper to lift the bars out of the pan and cut into squares.\n\nServe and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="spinach_chicken_recipe_intro">This Spinach Chicken recipe is a healthy and delicious meal that\'s perfect for a quick and easy dinner. It\'s packed with protein and nutrients from the chicken and spinach, and the creamy sauce adds a touch of indulgence without being heavy.</string>
    <string name="spinach_chicken_image">spinach chicken image</string>
    <string name="spinach_chicken_ingredients">• 4 boneless, skinless chicken breasts\n• Salt and pepper, to taste\n• 2 tablespoons olive oil\n• 2 cloves garlic, minced\n• ½ cup chicken broth\n• ½ cup heavy cream\n• ½ cup grated Parmesan cheese\n• 2 cups fresh spinach, chopped\n• ¼ teaspoon red pepper flakes (optional)</string>
    <string name="spinach_chicken_instructions">1. Season the chicken breasts with salt and pepper on both sides.\n\n2. Heat the olive oil in a large skillet over medium–high heat. Add the chicken and cook for 5–6 minutes per side, until golden brown and cooked through.\n\n3. Remove the chicken from the skillet and set aside.\n\n4. In the same skillet, add the garlic and cook for 1–2 minutes until fragrant.\n\n5. Add the chicken broth to the skillet, scraping the bottom of the pan to release any browned bits.\n\n6. Add the heavy cream, Parmesan cheese, and red pepper flakes (if using) to the skillet. Stir to combine.\n\n7. Bring the sauce to a simmer and cook for 3–4 minutes, until thickened.\n\n8. Add the chopped spinach to the skillet and stir until wilted.\n\n9. Return the chicken to the skillet and spoon the sauce over the top.\n\n10. Cook for an additional 1–2 minutes to heat the chicken through and serve.</string>
</resources>